<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>LimeChat</title>
    <link>http://limechat.sourceforge.net/</link>
    <description>Change Log of LimeChat</description>
    <language>en-us</language>

    <item>
      <title>0.19</title>
      <link>http://limechat.sourceforge.net/index_ja.html#v0.19</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2008 00:13:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
  			<ul>
  				<li>Make bouncing just one time for highlight.</li>
  				<li>Added badges on the icon for highlight or new talk.</li>
  				<li>Assigned cmd+ctrl+0..9 to move to the nth server.</li>
  				<li>Changed to disconnect from all servers when the computer is going to sleep.</li>
  				<li>Changed to reconnect to the servers after waking up.</li>
  				<li>Added /timer command. (e.g. /timer 5 join #limechat)</li>
  				<li>When updating the channel list, perform sorted insert instead of re-sorting.</li>
  				<li>Search channel topics in the Channel List.</li>
  				<li>Added "first" attribute for span.sender to show nicknames in the first line only.</li>
  				<li>Changed to ignore CTCP replies with empty commands.</li>
  			</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>0.18</title>
      <link>http://limechat.sourceforge.net/index_ja.html#v0.18</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2008 22:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
  			<ul>
  				<li>Added exact word matching for highlighting.</li>
  				<li>Added SSL support.</li>
  				<li>Added alternative nicknames support.</li>
  				<li>Implemented drag and drop files on the member list to send files on dcc.</li>
  				<li>Added fallback encoding.</li>
  				<li>Changed Cmd-w to close current panel with confirmation when the panel is a channel.</li>
  				<li>Added Kick, Ban and Kick &amp; Ban in the context menu on the member list.</li>
  				<li>Assigned Cmd+E to copy the selection.</li>
  				<li>Changed priority of Growl notifications to 1 for highlight events.</li>
  				<li>Added 'New Folder' button on the open dialog for transcripts location.</li>
  				<li>Changed to not use nick format for transcripts.</li>
  				<li>Changed the format of text messages for Growl notifications to "&lt;nick&gt; msg".</li>
  				<li>Changed to order front the main window when clicked on a growl notification.</li>
  				<li>Assigned enter key to send text on the paste dialog.</li>
  				<li>Added opt-up/down for moving around histories.</li>
  				<li>Changed to not allow '?' at the end of URLs.</li>
  				<li>Changed to select an existing talk when trying to start a talk again.</li>
  				<li>On the paste dialog, changed "Privmsg command" and "Notice command" to "Send to channel" and "Send Notice to Channel" respectively.</li>
  				<li>Changed /part without parameters to close the current talk.</li>
  				<li>Changed to handle /whois to get more information.</li>
  				<li>Added /rejoin, /cycle and /hop commands to rejoin the current channel.</li>
  				<li>Added /op, /deop, /halfop, /dehalfop, /voice, /devoice, /ban, /unban, /umode, /raw and /quote commands.</li>
  				<li>Added aliases, /t for /topic and /leave for /part.</li>
  				<li>Added /j command to join a channel.</li>
  				<li>Renamed /ctcpquery to /ctcp.</li>
  				<li>Removed /ctcpping.</li>
  				<li>Added nick attribute to the console log.</li>
  				<li>Changed to set 'server' type attribute for server logs like &lt;body type="server"&gt;.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a nil access bug in DccManager#tableView_objectValueForTableColumn_row.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, 'Override Log Font' option should be applied to body[type=...] and body.(normal|console) elements.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, numeric values should be capped when converting from ruby to objc.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, parameters for Time.at should be Fixnum.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, marked scrollers were visible on the top-left corner of log views when initialized.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, the scrollers of log views won't be rendered correctly when initialized with not enough frame.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, "MODE +a user" should be considered as setting an user mask.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, my address was forgotten after reconnecting.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug in utf-8 string validator.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, log views dropped received lines before initializing.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, 'Reveal in Finder' menu action on the dcc dialog caused an exception.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, 'Highlight your current nickname' option should be applied for the console log.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, /query command should be cleared after opening a talk.</li>
  			</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>0.17</title>
      <link>http://limechat.sourceforge.net/#v0.17</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 21:51:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
  			<ul>
  				<li>Fixed a crashing bug on 10.4, when pushed [+] button on the startup dialog.</li>
  				<li>Implemented drawing highlight indicators on a vertical scroller of log views.</li>
  				<li>Enabled continuous spell checking by default.</li>
  				<li>Now we can rearrange servers and channels on the server tree.</li>
  				<li>Added a filter text field on the channel list dialog.</li>
  				<li>Added an option, "Auto accept file transfers".</li>
  				<li>Added "Open File" menu item for receiving items on the dcc dialog.</li>
  				<li>Added "Reveal in Finder" menu item for receiving items on the dcc dialog.</li>
  				<li>Assigned double click to reveal a file in Finder on the dcc receiving transfer list.</li>
  				<li>Reformed main menu.</li>
  				<li>Assigned cmd+W to "Close Current Panel" when the main window is active.</li>
  				<li>Added a menu item, 'Copy Log as HTML'.</li>
  				<li>Added a menu item, 'Mark All as Read'.</li>
  				<li>Changed shortcut key for 'Mark Scrollback' to cmd+L, and 'Clear Mark' to cmd+shift+L as well.</li>
  				<li>Changed to show the paste dialog on opt-return.</li>
  				<li>Changed to select 'privmsg' as the default syntax when the paste dialog is not for paste.</li>
  				<li>Reformed the html template for log views.</li>
  				<li>New style action messages.</li>
  				<li>Moved the themes directory from '~/Library/LimeChat/Theme' to '~/Library/Application Support/LimeChat/Themes'.</li>
  				<li>Changed the default nick format to '%n: '.</li>
  				<li>More smaller font for the member list.</li>
  				<li>Removed '*' in the head of system messages.</li>
  				<li>Removed a server name from place part in the console log.</li>
  				<li>Now mIRC color effects can be styled in css.</li>
  				<li>Added "colornumber" attribute to span.sender for coloring each nick with different colors.</li>
  				<li>Added "identified" attribute in log view's html for CAPAB IDENTIFY-MSG support.</li>
  				<li>Added HTML4 color names support for YAML themes.</li>
  				<li>Changed to allow rgb() and rgba() strings in YAML theme files.</li>
  				<li>Changed /query without parameters to close the current talk.</li>
  				<li>Changed to remember the current text if modified when pushed up key.</li>
  				<li>Now a scroll position is kept when received a new line and removed the first line.</li>
  				<li>Changed to retain input text when changed the current channel, and restore it when come back to the channel.</li>
  				<li>Use the current username for nick on the startup dialog.</li>
  				<li>Added support for CAPAB IDENTIFY-MSG and CAPAB IDENTIFY-CTCP.</li>
  				<li>Now 401 error is printed in a talk log when there is a talk item for the target.</li>
  				<li>Don't change servers when closing a channel.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, an effect stopping character should not render as an end tag when there is no effect.</li>
  				<li>Fixed a bug, the input text field should be scrolled on nick completion.</li>
  			</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>0.16.2</title>
      <link>http://limechat.sourceforge.net/#v0.16.2</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2008 11:54:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
  			<ul>
          <li>Added new connection dialog for the first start up.</li>
          <li>Added +q/+a channel modes support for Unreal IRCd.</li>
          <li>Added /query support.</li>
          <li>Added an option, don't show notifications when the application is active.</li>
          <li>Prohibit adding a member when received join in a mode +a channel.</li>
          <li>Changed to clear member list when received mode +a.</li>
          <li>Changed to rebuild member list when received mode -a.</li>
          <li>Changed to keep selection when a log view become not focused.</li>
          <li>Added note for the encoding setting.</li>
          <li>Fixed a method not found bug while formatting '%@'.</li>
  			</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>0.16</title>
      <link>http://limechat.sourceforge.net/#v0.16</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2008 17:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
  			<ul>
          <li>Fixed a number format bug, "0.format_size" caused an exception.</li>
          <li>Changed to send whois for a pointed member when doubleclicked on the member list.</li>
          <li>Improved the report dialog of SACrashReporter.</li>
  			</ul>
      ]]></content:encoded>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
